<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journals on Satrio Blog</title>
    <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journals on Satrio Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 17:42:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design System</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/design-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 17:42:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/design-system/</guid>
      <description>Design Sytems What&amp;rsquo;s a design system? In my words, it is a set of components and resuable code that team&amp;rsquo;s use to establish a brand identity and allow for more consistency and efficentcy for teams to build out pages, apps etc.
I found that the company I work for is growing through some major growing pains and I am super happy to be apart of the growth. I have a chance everyday to make a big difference in our success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Trip SF 2019</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 14:38:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/conf/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Conference 2019 Trip to SF I have returned from the Smashing Conference in the beautiful San Francisco, CA. Bay area in the house. I want to write down some of the experiences and highlights I gathered from this great experience.
It was a two-day gathering of some of the best minds in Front End/UX Design. Being a Front End Dev, myself, this was a perfect way to get out to the Bay and learn from the best in the biz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio 2.0</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/portfolio-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 17:57:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/portfolio-update/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Newest Portfolio! I have finally finished my rebranded portfolio. I decided to rebrand myself and take everything I have learned over the last year and apply it here. I did a lot of studying on UI/UX Design over the last year. Sadly more than actual coding. I still code on a daily basis at my real job but not enough JavaScript as I&amp;rsquo;d like. I think it would be super beneficial for me, where I&amp;rsquo;m at right now to learn the best design practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript30</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/javascript30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:31:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/javascript30/</guid>
      <description>Hey to all! Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;m starting to generate some people to this blog. I&amp;rsquo;m making it a goal to continue to write and post helpful tips as I learn and grow as a Dev. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working really hard on my Design skills. It was serisouly needed. Color Theory, Typography, the new trends etc.
With that being said, I am starting Wes Bos&amp;rsquo; JavaScript30 course which is 30 days of straight JS with daily challenges and tuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/graphic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 22:58:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/graphic/</guid>
      <description>Check out my new graphic for when I stream my favorite game Overwatch! Done in Adobe Spark &amp;amp; with Photoshop, I used a deviant Art, slapped on a filter, added a clean two clean fonts, and cropped in my photo.
I will be using it to blast out on Social Media when I play as my favorite character Sombra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Portfolio</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 15:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new Portfolio! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to have built out this beautiful site from complete scratch. Literally. Started it about 5 months from this post date and chipped away at it day by day. The main purpose is to showcase how much I have improved since I landed my first ever Front End gig full time. I will for sure post more this time, whether it be trips I go on or concerts I go to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cards Design</title>
      <link>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 16:04:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>satriowibowo1701.github.io/journal/cards/</guid>
      <description>#success-box {background: linear-gradient( 135deg, #81FBB8 10%, #28C76F 100%);}#error-box {background-image: linear-gradient( 135deg, #FF9D6C 10%, #BB4E75 100%);}#cat-box {background-image: linear-gradient( 135deg, #EE9AE5 10%, #5961F9 100%);}.cat-text {color: #5961F9;}.card-box {border-radius: 20px;box-shadow: 5px 5px 20px #cbcdd3;perspective: 40px;display: flex;flex-direction: column;justify-content: center;align-content: center;align-items: center;text-align: center;padding: 40px 20px;}#card-container {display: grid;grid-template-columns: repeat(auto-fit, minmax(250px, 1fr));grid-gap: 40px;max-width: 800px;margin: 60px auto;padding-left: 15px;padding-right: 15px;}.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
